Guide to the Antonio Márquez Papers, 1877-2010 (bulk 1932-2010)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IX. Printed Material
  - P. Cornelii Taciti, Berolini - Apud S. Calvary Eiusque Socium (book includes handwritten notes and marginalia), 1877 (Folder 58.4)
- Series X. Photographs
  - Artwork - Self Portraits, 1980 (Folder 59.1)
  - Bogata, Columbia — by Jorge Silva, undated; (14 prints) (Folder 59.2)
  - Family, Friends - Hyde Park, NY, 1980s-2000 (Folders 59.4 – 59.9)
  - Family, Friends - Spain, 1950-1960 (Folder 59.10)
  - Friends, Colleagues - Spain, 1995 (Folders 59.11 – 59.12)
  - Portraits – Friends/Colleagues, 1950-2000 (Folder 59.13)
  - Portraits - Work/Career, 1970, 1980 (Folder 59.14)
  - Family, Edgar Family, circa 19th century (Folder 60.5)
  - Spain, undated (Folder 60.6)
  - Unidentified photos, 2004; (2 CDs) (Folder 59.3)